# Anton Saad Farag Allah

Cyber security Engineer.

tonysaad1998@gmail.com 🔀

01280995186

Egypt Q

06 July, 1998 🏥

linkedin.com/in/tony-saad-0617891a7 in

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Graduated From Faculty of law**Beni Suef university

2016 - 2020

#### INDEPENDENT COURSEWARE

- CompTIA Linux +
- (Free4arabs Eng Walaa Isam (Youtube))
- CompTIA Network +
- YouTube
- Certified Ethical Hacker (CEH)
- Network Penetration Testing
- Pentester Academy
- Offensive Security Certified Professional (OSCP)
- Heath Adams
- Penetration Testing With Kali Linux (PWK)
- PWK version 2020
- Web Application Penetration testing
- Network Monitoring And Analysis
- Pluralsight
- Introduction to Firewalls
- Pluralsight

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **T-Parthenos Repairing Shop**

Hardware and Software Maintenance

02/2017 - 03/2020

#### Maydoum Net Selling Security Cameras

03/2018 - 09/2018

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Network Penetrationn Testing

Capture The Flag (CTF)

Good knowledge with Linux

My Arsenal : Metasploit Exploitaion Framwork, Burp Suite , Acunetix Vulnerability Scanner

#### **PROFILE**

Information Security Engineer started searching from scratch in ( How to hack ? ) having years of experience in network penetration testing , a fair knowledge with reverse engineering , android penetration testing and web app penetration testing . Searching for job opportunity in well known Company to make a difference and develop me knowledge .

#### **PERSONAL SKILS**

- Works under pressure
- Quick learner
- Patient
- Persuasive
- self learner
- self motivated

### **LANGUAGES**

English

Professional Working Proficiency Arabic

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

# **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES**

Python

(C)

**Bash Scripting**